b2bpay.co 2019-12-15

# Privacy Policy | B2B Pay powered by Barclays

Thank you for visiting our website and your interest in B2B Pay (hereinafter referred to as the "Bank"). Protecting your privacy when using our website is important to us.  
We are committed to making sure that any information you provide on our website or platform will be treated with the utmost confidence.

The purpose of this privacy policy is to inform you about the type, scope and purpose of the collection, processing and use of personal data. We would therefore like to ask you to take note of the following information:

* ###### Data controller

The data controller within the meaning of section 3 (4) of the Finnish Personal Data Act (523/1999) (PDA) is B2B Trade Payment Services AB, c/o Bilanssi Ltd, Mannerheimintie 15a B 00260 Helsinki, Finland. For questions relating to the collection, processing and use of personal data, you can get in touch with us via the postal address provided or via email at [privacy@b2bpay.co](mailto:privacy@b2bpay.co).

* ###### Purpose of data protection

The purpose of data protection within the meaning of section 3 of the Personal Data Act (PDA) is to protect personal data. Personal data refers to any information concerning the personal or material circumstances of an identified or identifiable natural person (data subject). An identifiable person is one who can be identified, directly or indirectly, e.g. using data necessary to complete a business transaction. This includes, for example, your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address and other data required to complete the transaction. This does not include data that cannot be used to identify any particular individual.

* ###### Anonymous access

You can visit our website without disclosing any personal data. Whenever you visit our website the data of your visit will be automatically stored in a log file ("log data"). Anonymously, we learn only your IP address, the website from which you visit us, the websites you visit on our site, the retrieved files, and the date and time of the visit.This data will be evaluated for statistical and market research purposes. The IP address is stored for security reasons. If it is to be used for marketing purposes, it is anonymized in advance.

* ###### Collection and storage of personal data

We collect, process and use your personal data in accordance with this privacy policy as well as the applicable Finnish data protection laws. We will only collect the personal data that you choose to disclose for specific purposes, e.g. to respond to your queries when prompted.

If you send us personal data by email or by completing electronic forms, you do so on a voluntary basis. Our trained staff shall treat your personal data with the strictest of security and process and store the data only for the respective purpose.

We only collect, process and use personal data that you provide us with on a voluntary basis, i.e. by completing an electronic form or by sending us an email, for the specific purpose you have submitted the data to us e.g. to register for personalized services, answer queries, account openings or account management, technical administration or performance of contractual relationships. The personal data will only be stored until the purpose it was collected for is fulfilled, respectively as long as we are required by law to store the data.

The personal data will be used to provide financial and other services. If you have explicitly given your consent, you will also receive product information.

It’s important to remember that ultimately, you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your password and any personal information.

* ###### Cross-border and priority transfers

In the case of cross-border transfers, the data contained in the transfer document is forwarded to the beneficiary’s bank via the Society for Worldwide Interbank Financial Telecommunication (SWIFT) in Belgium. For reasons of system security, SWIFT temporarily stores transaction data on payments in its two data centres in the Netherlands and the United States.

* ###### Disclosure of data

Personal data you disclose to us via our website or by email (e.g. your name and address or email address) will only be used to communicate with you and for the specific purpose you provided it for.

Without your consent, we will disclose personal data in addition to the cases specified in this privacy policy in the following cases:

If it is necessary to prosecute a case, personal data may be disclosed to law enforcement agencies, as well as any damaged third parties. Nevertheless, this is subject to the provision of specific evidence of unlawful or abusive conduct. Personal information may also be disclosed when this is necessary to assert they terms and conditions of use or other agreements.

We are also required by law to provide information to certain public authorities, such as law enforcement, financial authorities, authorities that can impose fines for administrative offences upon request.

Where we use third party service providers to provide services, e.g. customer services or the hosting of our websites or apps or certain system components (ID verification, sanctions screening etc.), on our behalf as part of contract data processing, we disclose information to these companies or individuals to the extent necessary to fulfil their contractual duties.

All external service providers are carefully selected and checked for compliance with contractual requirements and the provisions of the Personal Data Act. All external service providers are required to treat the information in accordance with this privacy policy and applicable data protection laws and regulations. They have signed agreements obliging them to comply with data protection laws and regulations and are not considered to be third parties within the meaning of the Finnish Perosnal Data Act. We do not sell or disclose your personal data to third parties. Banking secrecy and confidentiality of the data will be maintained throughout this process.

* ###### Cookies

B2B Pay uses cookies to respond to your individual needs more effectively. Cookies are small text files that are sent by our web server to your computer and stored there allowing the website to recognise you when you revisit the website. We use cookies in some areas of the website in order to improve your user experience. When you visit our website again, the cookie allows you to be recognised and tailor our services to your needs.

We work with our business partners who help us to make our products and services and the website more interesting for you. This means that when you visit our website cookies from our business partners will also be stored on your hard drive. The cookies stored in this way will be deleted automatically after a specified time. The data collected using a cookie ID will enable our advertising partners to deliver relevant advertising to you, when applicable.

You can prevent cookies from being stored on your computer by configuring your browser not to accept cookies, notify you automatically when sites try to store cookies or to block all cookies already received. Please note that if you do this, some features of this website may no longer function properly. If you only wish to accept our cookies but not those from our service providers and partners, you can configure your browser accordingly.

* ###### Google Analytics and Google Tag Manager

This website uses Google Analytics, website analysis tools provided by Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway Mountain View, CA 94043, USA ("Google"). Google Analytics and Google Tag Manager use cookies. The information generated by the cookies about your use of the website is usually transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States.

Google will use this information on behalf of the operator of this website for the purpose of evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity for website operators and providing them other services relating to website activity and internet use. Google will not associate your IP address as transmitted by Google Analytics and Google Tag Manager with any other data held by Google.

You can prevent the collection of cookies by adjusting the settings of your internet browser; however, we point out that in this case you will possibly not be able to use our website to the full extent. Alternatively to blocking the data collection via browser-plugin or on mobile browsers, you can prevent the data collection by Google Analytics via an opt-out cookie.

For more information about Google and data protection, see the Overview of Data Protection and the Data Protection Policy of Google.

* ###### DoubleClick

This website uses DoubleClick by Google, a service by Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway Mountain View, CA 94043, USA (“Google”). DoubleClick by Google uses cookies to present ads which are relevant to you. For this, your browser is assigned a pseudonymous identification number (ID) to check which ads were displayed in your browser and which ads have been viewed. Using DoubleClick cookies allows Google and its partner sites only to serve ads based on your previous visits to our and other sites on the Internet. The information generated by the cookie is transmitted by Google to a server in the USA for evaluation and storage.

You may refuse the use of cookies by changing the settings on your browser; however, we point out that you may in this case not be able to use all the features of the site to their fullest extent. You can also prevent capture of the data generated via cookies and related to your use of the website (including your IP address) on Google and the processing of these data by Google by downloading and installing the browser plug-in for DoubleClick deactivation from Google. Alternatively, you can use the relevant settings on the TRUSTe website to register your objection. This page brings together from a range of advertising providers many options for registering your objection. Please note that in this case, after deleting all cookies in your browser, or the subsequent use of another browser and/or profile, the objection will have to be registered once again.

For more information about DoubleClick and the handling of personal data, please refer to the Privacy Policy of Google.

* ###### Google AdWords Conversion Tracking

This website uses Google AdWords Conversion Tracking, a service by Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway Mountain View, CA 94043, USA (“Google”). With this, the performance of provided advertising (so-called AdWords campaigns) is measured. By providing an analysis programme, Google can evaluate the performance of provided ads, and Google as well as we as a customer of Google can increase the quality and relevance of ads that our customers see. Google AdWords Conversion Tracking uses cookies. The information generated by the cookie is transmitted by Google to a server in the USA for evaluation and storage. In most cases, the cookies remain active on your computer for 30 days. When you visit our website during this period, Google and we are informed that you have seen the ad provided.

You may refuse the use of cookies by changing the settings on your browser; however, we point out that you may in this case not be able to use all the features of the site to their fullest extent.

For more information about AdWords Conversion Tracking and the handling of personal data, please refer to the Privacy Policy of Google.

* ###### Newsletter

We provide our partners and customers with information about us and our services. To receive the newsletter, you have to provide us with a valid email address. In addition, we need your prior express consent. We will verify that you are the owner of the specified email address or that the owner consents to receiving the newsletter. We will not collect any other data. This data will only be used to send the newsletter and will not be disclosed to third parties.

When you register to receive the newsletter, we will store your IP address and the date of the subscription for verification purposes in the event that a third party misuses the email address and subscribes to receive the newsletter without the knowledge of the authorised owner.

You may at any time revoke your consent that allows us to store your data and your email address and to use it to send the newsletter. To revoke your consent, please use the link in the newsletter to send us an email to that effect.

* ###### External links

Our website contains links to other websites. We do not have any control over the content of websites operated by third parties. The websites we link to are not governed by this privacy statement and the assurances contained therein.

* ###### Security

Websites where we collect personal data from our web site visitors are usually encrypted with your browser's built-in encryption module. These websites, including the transactional systems of B2B Pay, use technical and organisational measures to protect users against loss, destruction, access, modification or dissemination of your data by unauthorized persons. In addition, B2B Pay has implemented comprehensive security measures based on the latest technology standards. B2B Pay uses a firewall system to prevent third-party access. This state-of-the-art technology uses multiple layers of encryption and identification to prevent unauthorised access or interception of customer data during transmission. Personal data are encrypted before transmission. Any information you provide is stored on servers located in data centres in Germany and the Netherlands.

* ###### Protection of minors

This privacy policy extends to the use of this website by minors. We are aware of the particular importance of protecting the data of minors on the internet. Therefore, we do not knowingly collect or keep data on children.

* ###### Right to information, erasure of data and the right to revoke consent

Under Article 26 of the Finnish Personal Data Act, data subjects are entitled to request information about the personal data we store on you, its origin and recipients as well as the purpose of storing the data at any time.

If you do not agree with the storage of personal data, you have the right to revoke your consent to data processing and use at any time with effect for the future. To revoke your consent, you have to send us an email with "Data protection officer of B2B Pay" in the subject and stating your address and email address to [privacy@b2bpay.co](mailto:privacy@b2bpay.co).

In addition, you are also entitled to have your personal data corrected, erased or blocked. To have your personal data corrected, erased or blocked, please send the relevant request by email to [privacy@b2bpay.co](mailto:privacy@b2bpay.co) with “data deletion”, “data blocking” OR “data correction” in the subject line. To the extent permissible by law, we will either have the stored data erased or blocked or make the necessary corrections.

If you have any questions regarding the collection, processing or use of your personal data, data protection in general, or if you have any complaints, please contact our data protection officer by email at [privacy@b2bpay.co](mailto:privacy@b2bpay.co), who will be happy to assist you. We will make every effort to answer your questions as quickly as possible.

* ###### Disclaimer

We make every effort to keep this privacy policy up-to-date, and we, therefore, reserve the right to make changes to this privacy policy to provide clarifying information or to ensure compliance with legal and /or technical requirements. It is, therefore, important to refer to the most recent version of our privacy policy. You can print out the privacy policy without storing it at any time.
